chennaispider.com 2013-10-01

# ChennaiSpider.com privacy policy

* * *

**ChennaiSpider.com takes your privacy seriously. Please go through the following to know more about our Privacy Policy**

At ChennaiSpider.com, we know that you care how information about you is stored, used and shared. We do our best to keep your trust by using the information about you carefully and sensibly. This privacy notice explains our privacy policy. By visiting ChennaiSpider.com, you are accepting this privacy policy and our Terms & Conditions.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to **Contact Us**.

 **How do we use the information we gather?**

ChennaiSpider.com is a free community site and we publish almost all information we gather in this site. We do not share or sell your personal information to any third parties . But all personal information you submit as part of your public profile will be publicly accessible in our site, except the email address. We try not to publish your email address to avoid spam, but it is possible that in certain cases your email address may be exposed to public.

 **What kind of information we gather?**

We store any information you submit to our site. This includes, but not limited to, the profile you create at the time of registration, the resume you post in the job section etc. If you prefer not to publish any information, you may not submit it in the site. By doing so, you may be restricted from taking advantage of certain features of the site.

 **General visitor information**

For statistical purposes, we gather and store general visitor information like IP Address, Browser version, Visiting time, Duration etc. We may share such information with third parties or publish in our site for marketing purposes.

 **Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of information stored in your computer. When you login to ChennaiSpider.com, we store small cookies in your computer, to provide a better browsing experience for you. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use non personal about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

 **Advertisements**

We use advertisements from third party companies. We try to avoid any kind of offensive and harmfull advertisements in our site, but in many cases we do not have complete control of which advertisements appear in our site, due to the fact that many advertisements are automatically served by third party advertisers. We will not be responsible for any harms caused by such third party advertisements served in our site. However, if such issues are pointed to our notice, we will make all attempts to stop publishing such advertisements in our site.

 **Business Transfers**

As we continue to develop and grow our web site, we may sell ChennaiSpider.com or part of it. In such transactions, member information generally is one of the transferred business assets. 

**Contact Us**

If you like to contact the webmaster of this site, please **Contact Us**. We will get back to you as soon as we can.

 **SpiderWorks Technologies Pvt Ltd** **  
Kochi. India**

We would request you please provide us as much information as possible to resolve the issue.

* * *

| 

Online People

### Like Us?

 **Active Members**  
 _ **Today**_

 _ **Last 7 Days**_

 more...  
  
---|---
